[
    {
        "question": "What body of water is between Scotland and Denmark?",
        "answer": "The North Sea"
    },
    {
        "question": "What city is home to the Oriental Pearl Tower?",
        "answer": "Shanghai"
    },
    {
        "question": "What city is home to the Coit Tower?",
        "answer": "San Francisco"
    },
    {
        "question": "What city is home to the Milad Tower?",
        "answer": "Tehran"
    },
    {
        "question": "A bronze statue of whom stands at the foot of the steps to the Philadelphia Art Museum?",
        "answer": "Rocky Balboa"
    },
    {
        "question": "On which Hawaiian island would you find Diamond Head?",
        "answer": "Oahu"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only nation that borders both Andorra and Portugal?",
        "answer": "Spain"
    },
    {
        "question": "What style of architecture is the Empire State Building?",
        "answer": "Art Deco"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what city was `The Star-Spangled Banner` written?",
        "answer": "Baltimore, Maryland"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country contains the most forested area?",
        "answer": "Russia"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the official language of Guyana?",
        "answer": "English"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country has the longest coastline?",
        "answer": "Canada"
    },
    {
        "question": "KODAK is headquartered In what U.S. City?",
        "answer": "Rochester, New York"
    },
    {
        "question": "Xerox was founded in 1906 In what U.S. City?",
        "answer": "Rochester, New York"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the 4 US state capitols and states that begin with the same letter?",
        "answer": "Dover Delaware, Honolulu Hawaii, Indianapolis Indiana, Oklahoma City, Oklahoma"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which was the first suspension bridge over the River Thames in London?",
        "answer": "Hammersmith Bridge "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the second largest country in Africa?",
        "answer": "Democratic Republic of the Congo"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of South Korea?",
        "answer": "Seoul"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of the Canadian Province of Quebec?",
        "answer": "Quebec City"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the largest of the Canary Islands?",
        "answer": "Tenerife"
    },
    {
        "question": "Into what body of water does the Danube River flow?",
        "answer": "Black Sea "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Oman?",
        "answer": "Muscat"
    },
    {
        "question": "Muscat is the capital of which country?",
        "answer": "Oman"
    },
    {
        "question": "What bird is associated with Lundy Island?",
        "answer": "Puffin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is Gorky Park?",
        "answer": "Moscow"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Volta is the largest river in which country?",
        "answer": "Ghana"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the last Territory to join Canada?",
        "answer": "Nunavut"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Morocco?",
        "answer": "Rabat"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the world`s oldest royal residence still in use?",
        "answer": "England"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country has the most embassies abroad?",
        "answer": "USA"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country`s name once meant `Land of the Rabbits`?",
        "answer": "Spain"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the lowest elevation point in the Western Hemisphere?",
        "answer": "Laguna del Carbon, Argentina"
    },
    {
        "question": "What US state capital is located on the Hudson River?",
        "answer": "Albany"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many US states share a land border with Alaska?",
        "answer": "None"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Uruguay?",
        "answer": "Montevideo"
    },
    {
        "question": "Prudence Island is the third largest island in which US state?",
        "answer": "Rhode Island"
    },
    {
        "question": "The US shares a border with how many countries?",
        "answer": "Two"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state`s name is derived from the Chippewa words for `great water`?",
        "answer": "Michigan"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the world`s largest Buddhist temple?",
        "answer": "Borobudur, Indonesia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which bird is the national bird of India?",
        "answer": "Indian Peacock"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which bird is the national bird of Argentina?",
        "answer": "Rufous Hornero"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which bird is the national bird of Austria?",
        "answer": "Barn Swallow"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which bird is the national bird of the Bahamas?",
        "answer": "American flamingo"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which bird is the national bird of Belarus?",
        "answer": "White stork"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which bird is the national bird of Denmark?",
        "answer": "Mute swan"
    },
    {
        "question": "Sofia is the capital of which nation?",
        "answer": "Bulgaria"
    },
    {
        "question": "What five African countries border the Mediterranean Sea?",
        "answer": "Egypt, Morocco, Algeria, Tunisia, Libya"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Banff Airport is located in which country?",
        "answer": "Canada"
    },
    {
        "question": "On which sea does Romania have a coastline?",
        "answer": "Black Sea"
    },
    {
        "question": "By what name is the island of Rapa Nui better known?",
        "answer": "Easter Island"
    }
]